toilette-humor.com 2018-09-12

# Toilette-Humor.com Statement of Privacy

| 

## Your Privacy Is Very Important to Us

|   
---|---  
  
Toilette-Humor.com and Toilette-Paper.com have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices.

As you may have heard from your other favorite apps, new data protection laws are being launched all over the world (including GDPR in Europe). To keep pace with these new laws, Toilette-Humor.com is updated its privacy policy effective May 25, 2018. 

By continuing to use our services on or after that date, you acknowledge our updated Privacy Policy and agree to the updated terms.

**Our Privacy Promise and Policy**

We've updated our Privacy Policy to create more transparency and clarity including the type of information we collect and how that information is used. Our core commitments haven't changed including that we will never, ever ever, think of selling or sharing your information, we've just made it easier to understand. If you have any questions please contact [support@toilette-humor.com](mailto:support@toilete-humor.com).

**Collecting Data**

Toilette-Humor.com does not collect data within our own control. We use 3rd party services and apps for several online functions intended to help you within our website. The following are the 3rd party apps or outside services we use. Our website sometimes contains hypertext links to the websites of Third Parties for information purposes but we have no control over their websites and their privacy policies.

**Who controls your personal information on our website?**

  * **Robly Marketing:**  
Function: Maintains our subscriber list and sends our cartoon alerts  
https://support.robly.com/privacy-policy/  
When you sign up to receive our cartoon alert you are redirected to this outside service that gathers your information (name, email address and llist preferences) and keeps it there in a bulk listing until we are ready to construct and email a cartoon alert to you. We prepare our alert within their website and send it from there. It's easy to opt out. _See “You can opt out of receiving...” below._  

  * **Add This:  
**Function: Provides the ability for you to share a link from any of toilette-humor's web pages out through Facebook, Twitter (and many others), our email program, or an email function they provide.  
**How to opt-out from** any website that uses the “AddThis” third party app  

  * **Facebook Like Button, Amazon, Social media platforms and widgets:  
**Some third parties’ embedded content or plugins on our Site and/or Software, such as Facebook “Like” buttons, may allow their operators to learn that you have visited the Site, and they may combine this knowledge with other data they have collected about your visits to other websites or online services that can identify you. Certain built-in tools, such as Facebook’s Like button, may collect information such as IP address, location, or which page you’re visiting on our website via use of cookies. ****Data collected by third parties through these apps and plugins is subject to each parties’ own policies. We encourage you to read those policies and understand how other companies use your data. Any information or materials you share via a social media platform such as Facebook, Twitter, and Instagram is done at your own risk without any expectation of privacy.

**Facebook:**[How To Use Facebook Privacy Settings and Other Information](https://www.facebook.com/search/top/?q=privacy%20settings%20on%20facebook).

  * **Amazon Associates Program  
**We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites. **

Google Ads:

** We participate in the Google Adsense banner ads program, an advertising program also designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by allowing them to places ads on our website.

**General Information about advertising ads on our website:**  
Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies (together, Third Parties) who place advertisements on our Website and on the Internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about individuals. Except as expressly provided herein, we do not control Third Parties’ use of such technology and we have no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about individuals. It is up to you to familiarize yourself with the privacy practices of such Third Parties. 

  * **Third Party Links:**  
This Website and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the websites of Third Parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. Linked websites may contain links to websites maintained by Third Parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. We do not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such Third-Party websites. The inclusion of a link to a website does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization.

**YOU HAVE CERTAIN CHOICES ABOUT SHARING AND MARKETING PRACTICES.**

  * #### **You can opt out of receiving our cartoon alert emails or update your information and preferences**  
To stop receiving our promotional cartoon email alerts, email us at [s](mailto:talk@express.com)upport@toilette-humor.com (put unsubscribe in the title of the email) or follow the unsubscribe instructions in any promotional message you get from us. Be sure to use the email address you used to subscribe to us or we'll need to ask you if we can't find it. 

You can also update your information, change your email address or preferences by selecting the link at the bottom of any cartoon alert. The link says “Update Subscription Preferences”, or send an email to support@toilette-humor.com

  * #### **Several Ways You Can Control Cookies And Tracking Tools.  
**_Several Sources For Information (external informational websites):_  

[Stop Online Advertisers From Tracking You  
](ttps://www.komando.com/tips/12053/protect-your-privacy-against-online-advertisers/all)[Four Steps to Controlling How You're Tracked Online  
](http://www.slate.com/articles/technology/bitwise/2013/09/google_alt_cookies_how_to_control_how_companies_track_you_online.html) [How To Tame Your Web Cookies  
](https://www.kaspersky.com/blog/web-cookies-101/13857/) [How to Block Third-Party Cookies in Every Web Browser](https://www.howtogeek.com/241006/how-to-block-third-party-cookies-in-every-web-browser/)  

**A Personal Note:  
What happened to me when I blocked cookies from being stored on my Browser.**

This felt funny to me. I blocked my cookies about a month ago just because I thought it was a good idea. Then I promptly forgot that I'd even done it. Suddenly the internet look a whole lot different than I was used to. I didn't know why and I couldn't see any of the ads on our Toilette-Humor website. Then I paniced because I couldn't see any of the icons that allowed people to “share the webpage with a friend” either. It took me an entire day to figure out what had happened. 

Our browsers have a lot to do with whether we can allow cookies or not. You might want to turn them off (per some of the instructions above) and then test your browsing experience to determine if this is really what you want to do. 

### **OUR WEBSITES AND CHILDREN**

Our 3rd party apps are meant for adults. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can email us at support@toilette-humor.com. You can also write to us at the address listed at the end of this policy. Please mark your inquiries “COPPA Information Request.” Parents, you can learn more about how to protect children's privacy on-line [here](http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/privacyinitiatives/childrens_educ.html).   

### **YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS.**

If you reside in California, you have the right to ask us one time each year if we have shared personal information with third parties Iwhich we would never do) for their direct marketing purposes. To make a request, please email [s](mailto:talk@express.com)upport@toilette-huorc.om and include the title “California Privacy Rights” in the subject line.

### **WE USE STANDARD SECURITY MEASURES.**

We maintain reasonable administrative, technical and physical safeguards in an effort to protect against unauthorized access, use, modification and disclosure of personal information in our custody and control. However, the Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our sites or apps will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. This includes not sharing your passwords.

Our third-party service providers are given the information they need to perform their designated functions, and we do not authorize them to use or disclose personal information for their own marketing or other purposes.

### **CONTACTING THE WEBSITE:**

If you have any questions about this privacy promise, the practices of this site, or your dealings with us, you can contact the Web Administrator at support@toilette-humor.com.
